edustudies.com 2013-09-14

# Welcome to Edustudies.com

Edustudies.com understands that you are concerned about how your information is used and shared. This notice explains our privacy policy and how your information may or may not be used by our site.

By visiting Edustudies.com you are accepting the terms described in our privacy policy. 

What personal information about customers does Edustudies.com gather?   
Information we gather on our site helps us enhance the experience that future visitors may have on our site. Here are the types of information we gather:

  * **Information You Give Us**  
On our site, you will find a variety of forms. Each form pertains to a particular school or educational institution. Each form may collect information such as Name, Phone number, email address, postal address, gender, and age. Not all forms require all the information. You can choose not to provide the information, but you may not be able to complete the process of requesting information from that school. We use the information you provide to inform the schools of your interest and the best way of getting in contact with you. You will usually be contacted via phone or email by a representative of the school. You may request information from more than one school, which means you may be contacted by each school. We do not resell the information to any company unless you authorize us to do so, by agreeing to be part of the [Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com/) newsletter. This is not a required question to complete the form. 

We also want you to know that we do at times send the information to third party validation services to ensure all of the information is accurate and true. This helps us ensure that the schools which you are requesting information from have the most accurate way of getting in contact with you. 

  * **Automatic Information**  
We receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our site. Our site uses "cookies" like many other sites. This helps us determine what browser you are using and how to best present the information to you. Some automatic information examples are: browser type, operating system, IP address, and date and time of information request. You can disable cookies in your web browser, however this may affect the experience you have on our site, since you may not be able to see all of the features. The cookies we set do have an expiration date and will automatically be disabled after the expiration date. 
  * **Information from Other Sources**  
We do receive information from other sources and append this to the information that is sent to each school. Examples of this information are the following: Source of where you initially clicked on an advertisement, what you may have typed in, during your search at Google, Yahoo!, Ask, or MSN which spawns our advertisement. This information helps us better optimize our site based on your information needs. 

**Does[ Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com.com/) share the information we receive?**  
Information about our customers is very important to us. We do reserve the right to sell the information to other parties if you willfully agree to be part of our newsletter. However, we will only disclose your email address. 

The information that is submitted to each school is not subject to being sold to anyone else except the school you have requested information from. Our relationships and contracts with the schools prohibit us from contacting you directly without your expressed consent. 

**What sort of Information might I receive from[ Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com/)?**  
If you do opt-in to our newsletter, we may on occasion send out information that we deem of interest to you. This could range from helpful hints about education to other advertising offers such as but not limited to loan offers, and/or consumer product offers. 

If you wish to opt out of our newsletter, you can unsubscribe at any time by going to the following link: [Edustudies.com](http://www.edustudies.com/)

**What information can I access?**  
[Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com/) fully believes in transparency and accessibility. If you wish to delete your information from our database, please send a written request to contactus@edustudies.com and your request will be processed within 3 business days. 

If you wish to remove your contact information from a particular school, you must contact that school directly. You can also email us, and we will forward on your request to the appropriate representatives at each school. It usually takes about 1 week for all parties to comply with your request. 

**Are Children allowed to use[ Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com/)?**  
All people are allowed to access and use our site. However, since we market education for adult learners, we usually require the person to be at least 18 years old to submit an request for information.

**How safe is my information?**  
At [Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com/) we currently do not collect information such as social security numbers or credit card numbers. If we do in the future change this policy, we will ensure that this information is transmitted in a secure environment. At the moment, we only collect information that is publicly accessible and can often be found in phone books or internet search engines. Therefore, we currently do not offer SSL encryption on our site. 

**If I have a problem with my data, how can I resolve it?**  
We are committed to helping you resolve your dilemma as quickly as possible. Please contact us through email at contactus@edustudies.com. This email box is checked during business working days only. We are committed to resolving any issues in a timely manner. 

**Conditions of Use**  
By using and accessing [Edustudies.com](http://edustudies.com/) you are agreeing to the Online Privacy Policy set forth. As our business changes and grows, we may change the privacy policy. Any changes will be posted on our site. Please check back often for any updates.
